Guide to the Lewis and Clark Centennial and American Pacific Exposition and Oriental Fair Records 1894-1933
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- President's Office, Series 2
  - Correspondence, general
    - Moore and Short - Moores, W. A., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 11/18)
      Moore, W.H. (Reference Meeting)
      Moore, Willis L. (Weather Forecasts)
      Moorehouse, E.H. and Company (Paints, Moldings, etc.)
      Moores, Bertha (Reference Employment)
      Moores, W.A. (Secretary, Oregon State Fair)
    - Moran Bros. - Mossessohn, M., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 12/1)
      The Moran Bros. Company (Invite to Launching of Battleship Nebraska)
      Morey, W. (Consular Service, Ceylon)
      Morgan, A.L. (Souvenir Medals)
      Morgan E.E., Mrs. (Publicity)
      Morris, Chas. H. (Souvenir Spoons)
      Morris, James P. (Ticket difficulties)
      Morrison, E.U. (Model of Mt. Hood)
      Morrison, John P. (Season Pass)
      Morse, A.A. (Oregon Railroad and Navigation Company)
      Morse, Andrew J. (Fire Department Supplies)
      Morse, C.R. (Reference Envelope Design)
      Morse, M.B. (Shoes)
      Morse, S.G. (Indian Colony)
      Morse, W.H. (Capital Stock)
      Morton, Paul (Secretary of Navy)
      Morton, William (Salary)
      Moschel, Carl F. (Info Request)
      Mosessohn, M. (Portland Chamber of Commerce)
    - Moulton, Herbert F. - Myers, Jefferson, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 12/2)
      Moulton, Herbert F. (Request for Photographs)
      Mowry, Geo. H. (Catalogue)
      Mt. St. Joseph's Home for the Aged
      Muckley, E.S. (Publicity)
      Mueller, Otto (Reference E.B. Gaze)
      Muir, Charles S. (Reference Fees/Concessions/Engraving)
      Muir, Thos. King (Reference Mining Congress)
      Multnomah Printing Company
      Multnomah Rod & Gun Club
      Murphy, Capt. Charles A. (Oregon National Guard Duty at Exposition)
      Murphy, J.J. (Clerk, State of Oregon)
      Murphy, James H. (United Irish League of America)
      Murphy, John Miller (Complimentary Press Pass)
      Murray, Charles (Reference Fred Walz)
      Mursching, Sebastian (Info Request)
      Myers, George Francis (Flying Machine, Columbus Air Navigation Company)
      Myers, Jefferson (Special Commission)
    - Narrington, James E. - Nevins, James, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 12/3)
      Narrington, James E. (Stamps)
      Nash, W.F. (Job Application)
      National Association of Railway Agents
      National Drill and Manufacturing Company
      National Education Association
      National Livestock Association
      The National Magazine
      Nebraska, Governor of
      Nebraska Lumber Dealers' Association (Bird Critchfield, Secretary)
      Nebraska Pavilion
      Nebraska Republican State Committee
      Nernst Lamp Co.
      Neustadter Bros. (Gate Passes)
      Nevins, James (Pinkerton's)
    - New Empire - Nicoll the Tailor, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 12/4)
      The New Empire, A Monthly Journal
      Newall, Anne (WCTU, Oregon)
      Newberry, S.A. (Reference Zoeth Houser)
      Newhall, Charles B. (Application for Superintendent of Manufacturers & Textiles Building )
      Newhouse, Hugo D. (Employment Request)
      New Jersey Corporation’s Agency (Info Request)
      New Jersey Corporation’s Guaranty and Trust Company (Info Request)
      New Jersey Registration and Trust Company (Info Request)
      Newman, Frank R. (Camera Receipt & Fair Admission)
      Newman, J.L. (Commemorative Diplomas)
      News
      New System Ticket Company
      New York Times (Saturday Review of Books and Art)
      New Zealand International Exhibition
      Nicholls, H.M. (Reference "The World's Work”)
      Nichols, Dennis (Trees reference Lewis and Clark)
      Nichols, Sam. H. (Washington Secretary of State)
      Nickerson, R. Ella (Design)
      Nickum & Kelly (Reference Sand)
      Nicoll the Tailor
    - Niedermarck, H. C. - Northern Pacific Express Co., 1902-1905 (Box-folder 12/5)
      Niedermark, H.C (Info Request)
      Niekein, Laura (Lewis & Clark Women's Club of McMinnville
      Nielsen, M.P. (Sculptor and Medal)
      Nightingale, Wm. (Decorative Arch)
      Niles, Edith L. (Lewis & Clark Civic Improvement Association)
      Nob Hill Citizens
      Noon, W.C. Bag Company
      Norris, A.H. (Publicity)
      Norris Safe and Lock Company
      North Dakota (draft of circular letter to state officials)
      North Pacific Lumber Company
      North Pacific Steamship Company
      North, S.N.D. (Statistical Atlas and Abstract, U.S. Census Office)
      Northern Pacific Express Company (M.G. Hall, Superintendent)
    - Northern Pacific RR Co. - Charlton, A.D., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Northern Pacific RR Co., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 12/7)
      Fee, Chas. S.
      Misc.
      Mott
    - Northern Pacific Terminal Co. - Novelty Sign Co., 1904-1906 (Box-folder 12/8)
      Northern Pacific Terminal Co.
      Northwest Electric Eng. Co.
      Northwestern Light Company
      Northwestern Transfer Co. (Reference Billing)
      Norwich Union Fire Insurance Society
      Novelty Sign Company
    - O'Brien, J. P. - Oregon Furniture, 1902-1905 (Box-folder 12/9)
      O'Brien, J.P. (Southern Pacific Lines in Oregon)
      O'Bryan, J. Harvey (Property Lease)
      O'Connor, J.J.V. (1905 Manufacturers Club)
      Oliver, Turner (Reference Jonas M. Church)
      Olds Motor Works
      Olympia, Washington Chamber of Commerce
      O’Neill, Hugh J. (Reference Position)
      Oosse, Peter (Info Request)
      Oppenheimer, Gen. L.M. (Reference Texas Exhibit)
      Oregon. Office of the Secretary of State (Attorney General's interpretation of legistlative act regarding the exposition, 1904)
      Oregon Commandery Knights Templer
      Oregon Federation of Women's Clubs
      Oregon Furniture Manufacturing Company
    - Oregon Railroad and Navigation Co., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 12/10)
      Calvin, E.E.
      Colton, W.W. (Attorney)
      Craig, A.L.
      Miller, R.B.
      Miscellaneous
      Mohler, A.L.
      Worthington, B.A
    - Oregon Round Lumber Co. - Orient Insurance Co., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 12/11)
      Oregon Round Lumber Company (D.C. O'Reilly, Manager)
      Oregon Short Line Railroad
      Oregon Smelting and Refining Compnay
      Oregon Daily Journal
      Oregon Statesman
      Oregonian
      Orient Insurance Co. (John P. Sharkey)
    - The Orientalist's International Union of the Pacific Hemisphere (C. Pfoundes), 1903 (Box-folder 12/12)
    - Orphans of St. Mary's Home - Owens, Lola, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 12/13)
      Orphans of St. Mary's Home
      Orr, Joseph H. (The G.P. Bhumgara Company)
      Osborne, D.M. and Company (Reference Capitol Stock)
      Osborne, Dorothy
      O,Shea, John F. (Union Meat Company)
      Ostrander, Mrs. C.L. (Reference a Claim)
      Otten, George (Plants)
      Otwell, W.S.
      Oudendijh, John (Introductory Letter/UPRR)
      Ovaitt, N.C. (Comptograph Company)
      Overland Monthly Publishing Company
      Owen, Thomas M. (Alabama Department Archives and History)
      Owens, Lola C. (Employment Request)
    - Pacific Athletic Assoc. - Pacific Coast Steamship Co., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 12/14)
      Pacific Athletic Association (Info Request)
      Pacific Blank Book Company (Stationers)
      Pacific Christian Advocate (See Rader, Daniel)
      Pacific Coast Biscuit Company
      Pacific Coast Casualty Company
      Pacific Coast Condensed Milk Company)
      Pacific Coast Electric Transmission Association
      Pacific Coast Forest, Fish & Game Association
      Pacific Coast Steamship Company
    - Pacific Express Co. - Packard, L. c., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 13/1)
      Pacific Express Company (Reference a Bill)
      Pacific Fisherman (Fisheries Exhibit)
      Pacific Mail Order Company
      Pacific Mail Steamship Company
      The Pacific Mutual Life Insurance Company of California
      Pacific Paper Company (Prices Typewriter Paper/Color Design)
      Pacific Regalia Company (Paul Pferdner)
      Pacific States Telephone Company
      Packard, L.C. (Info Request)
    - Paffrach, Kiaspar - Payn, Elias, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 13/2)
      Paffrath, Kiaspar (Info Request)
      Page, Walter H. (Doubleday, Page & Company Publishers, The World’s Work)
      Paget, B. Lee (Reference Geese on Lake)
      Pague, B.S. (Referral)
      Palouse Land Company (Reference Ben Burgunder)
      Palouse, Washington, Business Mens Association)
      Parker, W.D. (Space Inquiry)
      Parr, R.E. (General Agent–The Meyercord Company)
      Patten, G.H. (General Electric Company)
      Patterson, W.H. (Secretary, Floral Department)
      Patthey, Henry S. (The Minneapolis Journal)
      Patton, Grace (Reference a Coyote)
      Paul, E.C. (Application for Architect)
      Paxton, Ossian Franklin (Reference Capitol Stock)
      Payn, Elias J. (Chamber of Commerce, Olympia, Washington)
    - Peano, Felix - Peyton, C. B., 1903-1906 (Box-folder 13/3)
      Peano, Felix (Architect/Sculptor)
      Pearcy J.N. (Fertilizer)
      Peaslee Bros. Printers (Reference Official Symbol, L&C Exposition)
      Peaslee, G. R. (Reference Painting of Mt. Rainier)
      Peck, L.O. (Editor, Hamilton Rustler)
      Peddycord, G.W. (Reference Payment of $21.35)
      Peery, Archie (Reference Employment)
      Peigler, Irving W. (Reference Opening of Exposition)
      Pence, Lafe (Lumber/Property Lease)
      Peninsula Lumber Company (Reference Article/Publicity, F.C. Knapp, Secretary)
      Penrose, S.B.L. President, Whitman College
      Perfection Manufacturing Company (Info Request)
      Perine, Frederic G. (Human Life Publishing Company)
      Perkins, H.C. (County Surveyor, Grants Pass, Oregon)
      Perkins, Jane (Info Request)
      Perkins, Tom W. ( The Daily and Weekly Gazette)
      Perley, G.A. (Musical Composition)
      Peters, Rollo (Picture Exhibit)
      Peterson, Aaron (Claim)
      Peterson, Arthur A. (Magazine Travel)
      Peurs, S.E. (Reference Building Stone)
      Peyton, C.B.
    - Flueger, Frank - Pigott, Arthur, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 13/4)
      Pfluger, Frank (Water Tanks, Pacific Cooperage)
      Pfoundes, C. (See The Orientalist's International Union of the Pacific Hemisphere)
      Phelan, James D. (Reference Elizabeth Martin)
      Phenis, Elizabeth (Reference Visit)
      Philippine Exhibit
      Philips, H.B. (Info Request)
      Phillips, B.F. (Printer Design)
      Phillips, L.A. (Reference the Baltimore Maryland Advertiser)
      Phoenix, Harriet I. (Reference Article in Independent)
      Photographers’ Association of America
      Piaud, L. (Reference Boilers)
      Pigott, Corporal Arthur W. (Photograph City of Portland Airship)
    - Pilkington, L. B. - Portland Board of Trade, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 13/5)
      Pilkington, J.B. (Grower and Importer of Fine Nursery Stock)
      Pillsbury, E.S. (Reference Houghteling Visit)
      Pindat, Bruno (Reference Passes)
      Piper, E.S. (Reference Souvenir Tickets)
      Piper, George (Republican State Committee, Washington)
      Piper, George U. (Resolution)
      Pittock, Geo. W. (Reference Publicity)
      Pittock, H.L. ( Oregonian Delivery)
      Planches, Signor Mayor des (Royal Italian Ambassador)
      Platt, Honorable Thomas C.
      Pletcher, T.M. (Melville Clark Piano Company)
      Pneumatic Mattress & Cushion Company (Info Request)
      Poase, A.H. (Reference American Inn)
      Polk, R.L. and Company (Requisition)
      Poole Brothers Railway Printers (Price of Booklets)
      Popple, Walter P. (Delay in Arriving)
      Portland Blue Print Company (Voucher)
      Portland Board of Trade
    - Portland Club - Portland Paper Box Co., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 13/6)
      Portland Club (Info Request)
      Portland Consolidated Railway Company (F.I. Fuller, General Manager)
      Portland Credit Association (Tully Lawsuit)
      Portland General Electric
      Portland Hydraulic Stone Company (Bids for Fountains)
      Portland Labor Press
      Portland Paper Box Company (Price of Boxes)
    - Portland Post Office, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Portland Seed Co. - Putnam, J. B., 1902-1905 (Box-folder 13/8)
      Portland Seed Company (Grass Seed Bids)
      Post Special Delivery Co.
      Potter E.G. (Norfolk & Southern Railroad Company)
      Potwin, Clara B. (Info Request)
      Povey Brothers Glass Company
      Powell, G.M. (Info Request)
      Powell, The William Company (Brass Goods)
      Power Monthly (Electrical Effects)
      Powers Furniture Company
      Powers, Ira (Info Request)
      Prescott, A.W. ( Oregonian Correspondent)
      Press Clipping Bureau (United States)
      Price, E.M. (Info Request)
      Price, J.G. (Info Request)
      Printers, Printing of Vouchers, Leaflets, Requisitions, etc.
      Prior, Eugene (Shetland Ponies)
      Public News Release (Reference American Inn)
      Puget Sound Bridge & Dredging Company
      Purdy & Poole (Info Request)
      Putnam, Geo. (Welcoming Address)
      Putnam, J.B. (State Librarian, Salem)
    - Quackenbush, C. W. (Black Sand Tests), Quinn, F. W. (California Guide-Publicity), 1905 (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Rader, Daniel - Redman, Z., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 13/10)
      Rader, Daniel (Editor, Pacific Christian Advocate)
      Rafferty, D. Dave (Reference Employment & W.H. Elinger)
      Raley, James H. (Souvenir Season Passes)
      The Ranch (Publicity)
      Rand, D.H. (Reference Absence and Payment)
      Randall, T.P. (Postage Due)
      Randall, Wm. E. (American Baptist Home Mission Society)
      Randolph, John (Reference Pass)
      Rands, H.A. (Topographic Model)
      Rands, Honorable E.M. (State of Washington Senate Chamber)
      Raphael, T.V. (Reference Passes for Salvation Army)
      Rates by Railroad
      Rates on Exhibits for Lewis & Clark Expo
      Rau, Lewis (Secretary, Concordia Club)
      Read, Harold J. (Photograph)
      Reader, Dr. J.K. (Homeopathician)
      Redman, Z.M. (Mt. Hood Lilies)
    - Reed, A. D. - Replogle, Mark A., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 13/11)
      Reed, A.D. (Fossil)
      Reed, Charles J. U.S. Marshall (Juror Summons)
      Reed, Samuel G. (Portland General Electric Company Contract)
      Reed, Walter (Optician)
      Reed, Will T. (Chief Inspector)
      Reeves, Chas. (Reference Per Diem)
      Reid Brothers (Architects/Spreckles Band Stand)
      Reid, Logan H. (Reference Tapestries)
      Reid, Wm. (Prospectus, Portland, Nehalem & Tillamook Railroad Company)
      Reidt, William (Portland, Nehalem & Tillamook Railroad Company)
      Remington Typewriter Company
      Replogle Governor Works
      Replogle, Mark A. (Statements)
    - Rhenisch, M. A. - Robertson, W. E, 1905 (Box-folder 13/12)
      Rhenisch, M.A. (Info Request)
      Rhodes, Sam A. (Reference Monthly Bulletin)
      Rich, B.B. (Info Request)
      Rich, H.G. (Reference American Inn)
      Richards, B. (Secretary/Treasurer M.E.T. Exhibitors)
      Richards, L.B. (Employment, Mint Exhibit)
      Richardson, R.W. (National Good Roads Association)
      Richley, A. (Tropical Foliage)
      Ridenberg, Wm.
      Riersch Machine Company (Chimes)
      Ringler’s School of Physical Culture
      Ringling Brothers Circus
      Ristine, T.H. (Wabash College)
      Robb, W.A. (Reference Mrs. Kerrigan)
      Roberts, M.H. (Reference Passes)
      Robertson, W.E. (Advisory Committee)
    - Robinson, R. F. - Romeike, Henry, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 13/13)
      Robinson, R.F. (Reference Passes)
      Robson, Robert (Launch & Gondola Concession)
      Roche, M.J. (Denver & Rio Grande Railroad Company)
      Rockey, A.E. (Daughters of the American Revolution)
      Rockwell, A.G. (Return Receipt)
      Rockwell, Cleveland (Reference Meeting of Women’s Club)
      Rockwell, L.E. (Info Request)
      Rockwood, Arden M. (Portland Association of Congregational Churches)
      Roebling’s, John A. & Sons (Wire)
      Rogers, J.R. (Printing & Engraving)
      Rohrer, M.F. (Reference Newspapers)
      Rollins, W.E. (Thank You Note)
      Romaine, M.E. (Souvenir Sales)
      Romeike, Henry (Newspaper Clippings)
    - Rooks, J. W. - Rowden, E. B., 1902-1905 (Box-folder 13/14)
      Rooks, J.W. (Reference Hotel)
      Roosevelt, Ther. (Fair Entry Gate and Roller Chairs)
      Rorey, Benjamin (Info Request)
      Rosenberg, Carrie (Reference Possible Postponement of Exposition)
      Rosewater, E. (Editor, Omaha Bee)
      Ross, A.M. (Contract)
      Ross, Charles J. (Telegrams)
      Ross, Ethel (Maiden Hair Fern Roots)
      Ross, Morgan (Unable to Attend)
      Rotermund, H.A. (Price of Settees)
      Roundtree & Diamond (Reference Perkins Tract)
      Roundtree Publishing Company (Dixie Manufacturer)
      Rowden, Prof. E.B. (Info Request)
      Rowe & Martin, Prescription Druggists (List of Portland Druggists)
      Rowe, H.S., General Agent, C.M. & St. P. Railway
    - Rowe & Martin - Ryman, F. S., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 14/1)
      Rowe, T.J. (Info Request)
      Royal Exchange Assurance
      Rudolph, A.F. (Info Request)
      Rushton, W.J. (Reference Captain Lewis Burial Site)
      Russell & Blythe (Real Estate and Financial Brokers Reference Lease/Insurance)
      Russell, Israel C. (Info Request)
      Rustin, H. (Info Request)
      Ryan, J.H. (Manager The Forum Tacoma, Washington)
      Ryan, M.O. (Reference Lost Purse)
      Ryan, Thos. (U.S. Map)
      Ryan, Thomas F. (Publicity)
      Ryman, F.S. (Oregon Booklet Request)
    - Sacajawea Statue Assoc. - Sarvis, C. C., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 14/2)
      Sacajawea Statue Association
      Sacramento Valley Development Association
      Saesin, Louis (Reference Money Order)
      Saint Paul Fire and Marine Insurance Company (See Harrison, M.C. & Company)
      Samuel, L. (The Equitable Life Assurance Society)
      Sante Fe Railway. Co.; Jno. J. Byrne; A.G. Wells
      Sarvis, C.C. (Lewis & Clark Rooming Bureau)
    - Sayre, James - Senator Charles Fulton, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 14/3)
      Sayre, James V. (Endorsement)
      Schleget, Frank (Reference Claim)
      Scovill Manufacturing Company (Blank silver Coins)
      Sears, Alfred F., C.E. (Reference Passes)
      Season Pass Issuances
      Seattle Press Club
      Seattle Public Library
      Seattle, Washington Alaska Club
      Seattle, Washington Chamber of Commerce
      Security Savings & Trust Company (Reference Voucher)
      Senator Charles Fulton
    - Senator John H. Mitchell, 1902-1905 (Box-folder 14/4)
    - Shannon, A. M. - Southern Lumber, 1903-1906 (Box-folder 14/5)
      Shannon, A.M. (Reference Voucher)
      Sheffield, William M. (Secretary, Alaska Club)
      Sheldon, A.C. Special Agent Burlington Route
      Shelton, Washington Board of Trade
      Sheridan, R.S. (Reference J.P. Marshall)
      Simon, N.D. (Info Request reference visit of Attorneys)
      Simpson, E.M. (Reference Model of Discovery Ship Columbia)
      Smith, Dan (Endorsement)
      Smith, Milton W. (Reference Lawsuit)
      Smith Premier Typewriter Company
      Smithsonian Institution (Acknowledgement)
      Snake River Irrigation Company
      Snohomish County, Washington Executive Committee
      South Bend, Washington Commercial Club
      Southern Lumber Manufacturers Association
    - Southern Pacific Co. (Coman, W. E., and Fee, Charles), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Southern Pacific Co., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 14/7)
      Fields, L.R.
      Goode, H.W.
      Koehler, Richard
      Worthington, B.A.
    - Spokane Chamber of Commerce - Sutton, A. L., 1902-1906 (Box-folder 14/8)
      Spokane Chamber of Commerce
      Spokane Interstate Fair
      Sprague's Mercantile Agency (Reference Portland Industrial Exposition Debt)
      Standard Electric Co.
      Steel, Geo. A. (Reference Timber Statistics in OREGON Pamphlet)
      Steel, Will A. (Reference Alaska Exposition)
      Steele, Warren N. (North Dakota Exhibit)
      Stemler, H.E. (Agent for L & M Alexander and Company)
      Stevens, Lillian M. (National Women’s Christian Temperance Union)
      Stone, George R. (Lewis and Clark Stock)
      Sullivan, John L. (Reference Concession—See also series "Division of Concessions and Admissions—General Correspondence" below )
      Sunday Closing of Exposition
      Sutton, A.L. (Endorsement)
    - Tacoma Daily Ledger - Tolman & Kimball, 1902-1905 (Box-folder 14/9)
      Tacoma Daily Ledger
      Tacoma, Washington Chamber of Commerce
      Taggart, Edward T. (Reference Emil Strandberg)
      Tavney, James A., Washington D.C.
      Taylor, H.A., Assistant Secretary Treasury (Muir Controversy)
      Taylor, J. Liuzerne (Employment)
      Taylor Young and Company (Reference Tickets)
      Tennessee, State of
      Thompson, J.R. (Electrical Engineer Expo Grounds)
      Thornton, W.M. (Everett, Washington Chamber of Commerce)
      Tinker & DeGessen (Contracts for Sunken Gardens)
      Tolman and Kimball (Lewis & Clark Commission, Spokane, Washington)
    - Tozier Collection and Other Relics Inquiries, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 14/10)
    - Trans-Mississippi Congress, 1902-1905 (Box-folder 14/11)
      Includes Portland Commercial Club
    - Traveler's Protective Association of America, Trunk Line Association; L.P. Farmer; Rates, 1905 (Box-folder 14/12)
    - Tucker, H. St. - Typewriter Bids, 1902-1906 (Box-folder 15/1)
      Tucker, H. St. (Reference Frank L. Merrick)
      Tuerck, I.K. (Portland Art Metal Works)
      Turnbull, C.S. (Money Order)
      Turner, Wm. B. (United States Senate)
      Tuttle, B.B. (Exemption of Property/Taxes and Related Matters)
      Typewriter Bids, Report on
    - Underwood Typewriter Co. - Vanduzen, E. W., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 15/2)
      Underwood Typewriter Company
      Union Mutual Aid Association
      United States Customs Service (Dep Dir Mueller)
      United States Customs Service (Patterson)
      United States Division of Customs (Customs Circulars)
      United States District Attorney (Reference Counterfeit Coins)
      The United States Fidelity and Guaranty Co.
      United States Flag Company
      United States Government Board - Edwin, Springman, Trans. Clerk
      United States Government Board - General
      United States House of Representatives
      United States Incandescent Lamp Co.
      United States Press Clipping Bureau
      University of Oregon, Office of Registrar
      Vanduzen, E.W. Company (See Chimes)
    - Wabash Railroad - Walker, Cyrus H., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 15/3)
      Wabash Railroad Company
      Wade Brothers (Architects)
      Wade, M.S. (Editor, The Inland Centennial)
      Wade, W.W. (Criterion Concession Company)
      Wadhams and Company (Souvenir Tickets)
      Waer, Edgar S. (Japamar Pharmacal Company)
      Waggener, F.W. (Reference Cost of Music)
      Wagner, H.G. (Publicity)
      Wagner, Paymaster (Reference F.L. Lonergan)
      Wahlberg, Hans C. (Oregon Hop Company
      Wakefield, Fries and Company (Reference Versteeg Property)
      Wakefield, John A. (Reference Tozier Collection; See also Tozier Collection)
      Wakeman & Morse (Bill Reference Cash Registers)
      Walden, G.N. (New York Life Insurance Company
      Walker, C. Howard (Info Request)
      Walker, Cyrus H. (Oldest White Man Born West of Rocky Mountains)
    - Wall, H. E. - Washington State Fair, 1903-1906 (Box-folder 15/4)
      Wall, H.E. (Info Request)
      Wall, P.T. (Shippers and Travelers Exchange)
      Wallace, H.W. (Season Pass)
      Walla Walla Fruit Fair
      Walla Walla Washington Commercial Club
      Wallender, C.O. (Builders)
      Walsh, M.J. Company (Reference Lighting)
      Ward, W.S. (Cottle Heirs)
      Wardall, Elizabeth M. (Info Request)
      Warmoth, Frances (Reference Lost Hand Bag)
      Warner, W.P. (President, Nebraska State Commission)
      Warren, W.H. (Emergency Hospital Ambulance Station)
      Washington County News (Publicity)
      Washington State Commission (Lewis and Clark Centennial Exposition)
      Washington State Bankers Association
      Washington State Fair